Xenia Dennen papers, Inclusive: 1931-2016, undated, Bulk: 1986-1998
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Collected Materials, 1931-2000, undated; 2
  - Periodical Tserkovnyi vestnik Zapadno-Evropeiskogo Pravoslavnogo Russkogo Ekzarkhata/Le Messager de l’Eglise en Europe Occidentale, 1955 June-July (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Periodical Tserkovnyi vestnik Zapadno-Evropeiskogo Pravoslavnogo Russkogo Ekzarkhata/Le Messager de l’Eglise en Europe Occidentale, 1956 August-November (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Book Zhitie sviashchennomuchennika Mitropolita Serafima (Chichagova)., 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Book Tserkov’ i Mir. Obshchestvennoe sluzhenie Tserkvi. Osnovy Sotsial’noi Kontseptsii Russkoi Pravoslavnoi Tserkvi: Metropolitan of Smolensk and Kaliningrad Kirill, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Periodical Politiia, 1997-1988 Winter (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Book Religion in Russia After the Collapse of Communism: Religious Renaissance or Secular State. Symposium Series Vol 51: Kimmo Kaarianen, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Photocopies of Russian Religious Samizdat: Prayer book, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Photocopies of Russian Religious Samizdat: Handwritten music score Chant (1917-1970), undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Photocopies of Russian Religious Samizdat: Book of religious poetry, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Photocopies of Russian Religious Samizdat: Brief description of Pskov Monastery of the Caves: Reply to a friend’s written request, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Politics and Religion in Eastern Europe: Patrick Michel (1 of 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Politics and Religion in Eastern Europe: Patrick Michel (2 of 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Politics and Religion in Eastern Europe: Patrick Michel (3 of 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Book Church and State: The History of Legal Relations: Alexei Nikolin, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript The Keston Research Moscow Office Report: Leonid Finkelstein, 1992 October 21-December 10 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Literary Productions, 1992-2016; 3
  The series contains Dennen’s diaries of Keston Encyclopedia project field trips to various parts of Russia.
  - Moscow Diary, 1992 September 22-October 22 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Moscow Diary, 1992 May 29-June 29 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Report: “Keston College Moscow Office”, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Moscow Diary, 1993 February 2-18 and February 24-March 12 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Moscow Diary, 1995 January 31-February 15 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Moscow Diary, 1995 February 22-March 10 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Moscow Diary, 1995 June 20-July 4 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Diary, 1995 October 4-18 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Moscow Diary, 1995 November 1-16 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Report on Moscow Visit, 1996 February 25-March 8 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Moscow Report, 1996 May 31-June 14 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Moscow Diary, 1997 March 5-20 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Report on Visit to Moscow, 1998 June 10-29 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Moscow Diary, 1998 November 23-December 11 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Moscow Diary, 1999 January 16-30 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Moscow Diary, 1999 February 22-March 15 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Perm (the Urals), 2000 December (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Diary. Moscow, 2003 March 24-April 9 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Report on visit to the Altai Krai, Altai Republic, St. Petersburg and Moscow, 2003 September 5-30 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Visit to Moscow and Syktyvkar (Komi Republic), 2004 June 1-18 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Diary: Visit to Moscow, Vyatka and Nizhni Novgorod, 2005 June 8-23 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Russian Diary. Moscow, St. Petersburg, Novgorod Velikii, 2006 March 9-23 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Moscow, Tula Ryazan, 2006 October 12-30 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - St. Petersburg, Pskov and Staraya Russia, 2007 April 20-May 2 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Moscow & Saratov, 2007 November 5-17 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Moscow & Ekaterinburg, 2008 January 4-16 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip to Vladimir, 2009 January 4-15 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip to Vologda, 2009 March 17-25 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip to Russian Far East and Eastern Siberia: Blagoveshchensk, Chita, Ulan-Ude, Moscow, 2009 June 12-July 2 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip: Belgorod & Kursk, 2010 March (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip to Naryan-Mar (Nenetsky Autonomous Okrug), Arkhangelsk, Solovki, 2010 June (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Field Trip: Voronezh & Lipetsk, 2011 January (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip to Ivanovo, Kostroma & Nerekhta, 2011 June (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - CD. Xenia Dennen Russian Diaries, 1994-2004 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Field Trip: Kalmykia and Astrakhan, 2012 January 15-29 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Field Trip: Arkhangelsk, 2012 March (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Keston Encyclopaedia Field Trip: Ulan-Ude (Buriatia), Irkutsk, Krasnoyarsk, 2012 June-July (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Bryansk, 2012 November (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip: Volgograd & Uryupinsk, 2013 January 25-February 7 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip: Petrozavodsk, 2013 March (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Encyclopaedia Fieldtrip: Kamchatka, 2013 June 15-25 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip: Kemerovo & Novokuznetsk, 2013 November 16-29 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Kaluga, 2014 January (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Vyatka (Kirov), 2014 June (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Kaliningrad”, 2014 November-December (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Kostroma”, 2015 January (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Kalmykia, 2015 March (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to the Komi Republic”, 2015 June (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to the Mari El Republic, 2015 November (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Saransk, Republic of Mordovia, 2016 January (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Kurgan, Southern Siberia, 2016 March (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Murmansk, in the Arctic Circle (Zapolyar’e), 2016 June (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Nizhny Novgorod, 1016 October (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Novosibirsk, 2016 November (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Novgorod Velikii, 2017 April (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Magadan, 2017 June (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Kursk, 2017 October (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to Lipetsk, 2017 November (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to St. Petersburg, 2018 January (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopaedia Field Trip to St. Petersburg, 2018 March (Box 14, Folder 2)